一旦Adapter被初始化  让我们把它绑定到ListView上
Once the adapter is initialized, let's bind it to the list view. But
但是我们还没有ListView的引用
you may notice that we don't have a reference to the list view in our fragment.
只是把它定义在了布局XML中
It was only defined in the layout XML. The system takes and
系统会实现XML中的布局
inflates layout XML files. And
并将它们转换成一个倒树状的结构
turns them into a full view hierarchy with a root layout of the main activity at
Main Activity在树顶（或者说树根） 我们可以给树上的每个View设一个ID
the very top of the view tree. We can also assign IDs to each view in the tree,
不过你用不到的View可以不给它设
but it's not required if you don't need a reference to an individual view.
例如 这个图像View没有ID完全没问题
For example, this image view doesn't have an ID associated with it and
在Java代码中对应的Activity或Fragment中
that's okay. Within the Java code of the associated activity or
如果我们需要这个按钮的引用 可以调用findViewById
fragment. If we need a reference to the button, we can simply call findViewById,
它会一直向下遍历这个树直到它找到有这个ID的按钮
which will traverse down the hierarchy until it finds a view with the ID button.
然后会返回它 同样 我们可以遍历
And then it will return that. Similarly, we can traverse down the view
去用ID找LinearLayout这个容器
hierarchy to find the linear layout with the ID container, and then return that.
同样的 可以用ID来找这个TextView
We could do the same to find a reference to this TextView by traversing down
但是想必你已经注意到了 它的父元素容器的引用我们已经有了
the view hierarchy. But you'll notice that we already have a reference to
所以我们能直接对父元素调用findViewById
the container which is a direct parent of this TextView. Hence, we can just call
然后用ID找到它对应的子元素
container.findViewById to search this subtree to find the TextView with this ID,
然后返回它  使用这个方法  我们要搜索的树
and then return it. With this method, we have a smaller sub-tree to search for
比起整个书更小
a given view, as opposed to searching the entire view hierarchy.
在Android Java文档中对于View这个类的说明（下面有链接）
In the Android Java doc for the View class, which is linked below if you want to
这里有个XML中定义好的按钮
follow along, it contains an example where the button with Define in Layout XML.
ID是my_button  在Activity当中
It was assigned an ID My Button. Then in the Activity, we can use the find
我们可以使用ID查找这个View  得到按钮的应用
view by ID method, with that ID, so that we can get a reference to the button.
然后我们可以动态地修改按钮 例如给它加一个监听器
Then we can change it dynamically, such as by adding a click listener to it.
在PlaceholderFragment.class中 将Adapter与ListView绑定
Now in the placeholder fragment class, bind the adapter to the list view.
幸运的是  我们已经给ListView分配了一个ID  所以很容易找到它
Luckily, we did assign an ID to the list view earlier. So, we can find it
使用最小的树来遍历找到它
easily now. Think about the smallest sub-tree in the view hierarchy that you
然后给它设一个Adapter 如果你想要点提示
can call find view by ID on. Then set the adapter on it. If you want an example,
可以看看下面的链接 做完后勾上复选框
you can see one in the link below. Check the boxes when you're done.